No more wine for me.
Neither the murky red.
Nor the bright one.
I’m thirsty.
Thirsty for my own blood.
Man: Are we getting there?
Woman: Yeah.
Man: Do you see him? He's waving at you.
Man: got all the bags?
Woman: Ah! Sorry...
...yeah, they’re all here.
Man: Bismillah! ("move forward!")
Man: What's he saying?
Woman: Asks if we are together...
Man: Say it's my wife.
Man: When did you stored these in the luggage?
Man: So, where is he?
Woman: Maybe he’s outside waiting, we’re late. Want me to go look?
Man: No, you stay right here.
I check.
Man: No praying room around...
Man: Hello?
Babak?
Can you hear me?
Hello?
For God’s sake!
Woman: What happened? Did it cut off?
Call him again.
Man: I don’t know where this boy is...
Woman: Well, maybe he forgot we’re arriving tonight...
Man: How do you mean, forgot? We’ve been planning this for 3 months now.
Man: Hello?
Hi Farideh.
We are well.
We’re still at the airport.
No worries.
Ok.
I’ll call once we get home.
Bye.
Woman: I have his address. Let’s just get a taxi.
Man: What if he’s not home?
Woman: Let’s just go to his home. We find a way.
Man: Wait in the street?
Man: I’m not wandering around a city where we don’t know anyone or the language!
Woman: We can’t stay here waiting till nightfall.
Man: We’ll wait till night if we have to. He said he’d come. He has to come.
Man: Wait, Pari!
Pari!
Pari: Babak?
Man: Wait till they pick up!
Man: What are they saying?
Pari: They’re speaking Greek.
Man: For God’s sake!
Man: Where have they brought us, a barn?
Don’t go in!
Pari: This is Babak’s handwriting!
Man: What?
Pari: That Babak left here three months ago.
Man: What do they want?
Pari: He owes them money.
Man: Apologize to them.
Official: When was the last time you saw your son?
Man: Two years ago.
Official: Has he ever mentioned any trouble with his university?
Man: No, Babak’s an excellent student. He’s here on a scholarship...
...at their best university.
University of Athens - Polytechnic.
Official: Yes, we’re aware. His name is on the embassy’s list,
but there seems to be a problem.
Man: What kind of problem?
Official: His scholarship has been revoked. It’s been over a year.
Man: Are you sure? He never told us anything.
Official: How come you haven’t seen each other in all this time?
Man: Babak’s been very busy. He didn’t have time to come back to Iran,
and we’re not the kind of family that travels abroad.
Official: If you don’t travel abroad, why send your son here?
Is anyone looking out for him?
Official: Hajji, I understand.
You’re a respectable family.
But we’ve seen this situation many times here.
Sadly, many of our youth lose their way
because of their freedoms.
so-called freedoms.
Official: Iranian students often drop out and don’t tell their parents,
just so they can keep receiving the scholarship money.
Official: Do you understand what I mean?
Pari: Babak would never do something like that.
Man: Sir, what can we do in this foreign city?
We don’t know anyo...
Official: Mr. Bagheri,
get the university’s address for Hajj Agha.
Bagheri: Right away.
Official: At your service.
Man: Why shaking head like that?
Pari: He didn’t enroll this year.
Man: Let’s go.
I told you, let’s go.
Man: What did they say?
Pari: Farrokh, wait!
Just listen for a moment.
Farrokh: I listened to you, and look where it got us.
Pari: You’ve been stressing yourself out for two hours. Calm down, it’s not good for your heart.
Farrokh: I’ll relax when I understand what’s going on.
You knew nothing?
Pari: No, I swear to God.
Farrokh: Don’t you swear!
He’s been lying to us for three years.
You never had any doubts?
Pari: Have I ever lied to you?
Farrokh: Why do you think he never came back to Iran?
Pari: I told you, he’s a young man... in a new country.
Farrokh: Student life… figuring himself out. You’ve been feeding me the same nonsense for years.
Pari: How is that my fault?
Farrokh: You insisted we send him to this damn place.
Pari: And you agreed to it.
Farrokh: What choice did I have?
No one would listen to me.
You filled his head with your fairy tales.
Pari: I only wanted what was best for him.
Farrokh: Well, there you go!
This is your idea of what’s best for him.
Are you happy now?
Pari: We still don’t know what happened!
Farrokh: What more do you need to happen? He’s left us in this strange city.
Pari: Farrokh, I know Babak. He wouldn’t do this without a reason.
Farrokh: Oh, I know how well you know him.
He brought us here to show us all this mess.
Farrokh: He’s destroyed our honor.
I’ve never been so ashamed in my life.
Pari: Enough with your honor and pride!
Farrokh: Now you’re mocking my honor?
Pari: To hell with your honor! My son is missing!
Farrokh: Last time you talked like this, you ended up in the streets
with a baby in your arms.
Astaghfirullah (seeking "forgiveness")
Pari: What do you want from me?
Farrokh: What do you want from me?
If honor doesn’t matter to you, why did you stay with me?
I didn’t force you!
Farrokh: Let’s go. We need to find a place to stay.
Bagheri: Unfortunately, the police have no trace of him.
Farrokh: How is that even possible?
Bagheri: His student visa expired a year ago. He’s been here illegally.
Farrokh: He’s been here for years. Can’t they do anything else?
Bagheri: Hajj Agha(Mister), it’s not that simple. He needs to be officially recognized as missing.
Farrokh: Please, see what you can do.
Bagheri: We’ll figure something out.
Farrokh[dreamy voice]: I didn’t force you!
You’ve been with me all these years, but you’ve always dreamed of a different life.
I didn’t force you! (dreamy)
Farrokh: What are you doing?
Are you okay, Pari?
Let’s go outside and get some air.
Bagheri: As soon as there’s any news, they’ll inform us. I emphasized that this matter is important to the embassy.
Farrokh: Thank you, sir. What else can we do?
Bagheri: Honestly, there’s nothing more we can do. We just have to wait.
Pari: No, sir. We can’t just wait.
Farrokh: Tell me, where do Iranians usually go here? What do they do? Is there a center? A mosque?
Bagheri: There’s the cultural center at the embassy, but your son had no connection with us.
As for the mosque, you might want to check out the church instead.
Farrokh: Why a church?
Bagheri: Hajj Agha, things are really bad here.
Farrokh: Speak freely.
Bagheri: Iranians here are in a terrible state. Many convert to Christianity to seek asylum.
Everywhere you go, you see addicted migrants.
Even our women and young men sell themselves for a bit of money
Farrokh: I understand perfectly.
Bagheri: Now, your son may not be caught up in all this, but I had to tell you.
Farrokh: So where do we even start?
Bagheri: Start with this area. It’s where most of the migrants are.
The Iranian shops here have the Zoroastrian symbol.
Many of them are involved in human smuggling.
If you see them, ask around, maybe someone knows your son.
Farrokh: ...Pari, don’t stand by the window... Pari, move away...
Preacher: The story is just beginning.
[Clapping]
God knows you’re not perfect.
But you’re the ones who started this journey.
[ Music]
No, unfortunately, I don’t know him.
Farrokh: Sorry for bothering you.
Woman: You’re not a bother. This is the house of God, and we are all His children.
[Worshiping]
Woman: If there’s anything we can do to help, we’d be happy to.
Farrokh: Nobody knows him.
Pari: Do you remember? He loved the sea.
When he was little, he used to say, “I want to be a pirate!”
Farrokh: It’s winter now. We won’t find him at sea.
You’re not eating, not sleeping well, and you’ve even stopped praying.
I’m more worried about you now.
We’ve been here a month already. We’re both on edge, and our money’s running out.
Wandering around like this is pointless.
Pari: But we’re not looking in the right places.
Farrokh: So where should we be looking?
Pari: I feel like Babak was running away from anything that reminded him of Iran.
He didn’t come back to Iran,
and he had no connection with the Iranians here either.
He didn’t even write in Persian anymore.
Farrokh: Then where do we search now?
What do you think?
Pari: I don’t know.
Farrokh: I love Babak like my own son.
He carries my name.
I’ll never abandon him.
I’ve asked Bagheri to prepare a request for Interpol.
If they find him anywhere in Europe or the U.S., we’ll be informed.
We’ll wait in Iran, and if they get any news, we’ll come back.
Even if there’s a 1% chance he’s still here,
we can hire a good private investigator.
Pari: Farrokh, I can’t leave here without Babak.
No more wine for me.
Neither the murky red.
Nor the bright one.
I’m thirsty.
Thirsty for my own blood.
spilled in the square.
Farokh: One more.
Farrokh: What are you doing?
Pari: I found this in Babak’s papers. See? It’s the same symbol as theirs.
Farrokh: What’s this symbol?
Pari: They've seen Babak!
Farrokh: Who are they?
Pari: How should I know? They’re just a group of young people. Farrokh, please. The girl said she saw him around here.
Farrokh: So she said something, why do you believe her? They’re just a bunch of thugs!
Pari: After all this searching, this is the only clue we’ve found.
Farrokh: You’ve lost your mind, and now you’re driving me crazy too.
Farrokh: What are you doing? Let’s go!
Pari: Farrokh, Babak has to be here.
Farrokh: Enough already!
[Whispering]
No more wine...
I’m so thirsty
Pari...
I was worried sick... where were you?
Pari: I thought it was Babak
... Farrokh?
What’s wrong? Are you okay?
Farrokh: I feel a little dizzy...
Pari: I couldn’t stop myself, I thought it was him.
I’m sorry.
Farrokh: No...
you should forgive me...
I wasn’t the father I should have been.
Pari: No, Farrokh, you didn’t fail.
Farrokh: I was just doing my duty.
That’s...
not enough to be a father.
I knew there was a danger
, but I still let him come here.
I wanted to be with you.
I wanted you to be mine.
Pari: I am your wife.
Farrokh: My wife?
You’re like them.
There’s something inside you.
I’ve seen it with my own eyes
, it’s torn so many lives apart.
So many good people lost...
I tried to protect you.
But now... the choice is yours.
Pari: Why are you talking like this, Farrokh?
You’re scaring me.
Farrokh: I don’t know.
My mind’s all over the place.
Come on, let’s go.
Tomorrow is another day.
Farrokh: Pari, make me some tea with candy.
Pari: Did you take your pill?
Farrokh: Yeah, but my stomach’s a bit upset.
Pari: Farrokh?
Farrokh? get up, it’s ready...
Farrokh?
Help!
Farrokh? Can you hear me?
Hold on, Farrokh!
Man: Hello, Miss. Pari? Why don't you pick up the phone??
Pari: He died in my arms.
Man: May God rest his soul.
Pari: It’s all my fault.
Man: No, no, no! Don’t blame yourself. Life and death are in God’s hands. This was meant to be. How are you feeling, Miss. Pari?
Pari: I have to find Babak.
Man: We’ve spoken to the embassy. They’re waiting for your call.
Man: That’s exactly what I’m saying.
I’ve talked to Mr. Bagheri, they’re aware of the situation.
Pari: They can’t do anything.
Man: Of course they can. Bagheri told me himself, they’re working with Interpol on the report.
Pari: They’ll never find him. Babak has changed. Only I can find him.
Man: But how can you find him alone?
Hello?
Pari: I need to burn.
Man: What do you mean, "burn"?
Pari, you’re in shock. We’re all in shock.
You need care right now.
Pari: I need help.
Man: Whatever you need, we’re here. You can count on me.
Pari: I need money. I have to stay longer.
Man: What?
Stay longer?
What are you saying? A woman alone in a foreign country? Have you lost your mind?
Please, go to the embassy. They’ll take care of everything. We’ll continue the search.
Hello? Are you listening?
Are you listening?
Listen, we can’t bring him back without you. His body’s still in the morgue.
The whole family is waiting here, they want to mourn him.
Pari: We will come back together.
All 3 of us.
I'll find Babak.
Man: What’s wrong with you? Has the devil gotten into you? Listen to me! You’re in danger too now.
No more wine for me—
Neither the murky red,
Nor the crystal-clear white.
I thirst for my own blood,
Spilled on the battlefield.
Strike with your sword,
Your sharp blade!
Strike!
Strike, until the head spins away from the body.
Build a mountain from these fallen heads,
Tear me apart!
Do not silence me!
Do not heed my words!
I must walk into the flames!
The fire, my child,
Yet I must burn,
So that I may become the fire.
Strike now, O bringer of chaos,
Break that jug upon the stone,
So I no longer draw from the flowing stream,
Nor dip my hands in its waters.
I will forsake the cup-bearer's task,
And let myself drown in the ocean.
I wanted him to live a way that I couldn't do myself.
I ...
never found the courage myself.
I always thought they wouldn’t allow it.
But the truth is, I didn’t dare to.